Congratulations Lomas Brown, man. Making
the next round here. Semifinalist.
I'm not saying this because I'm with the
Detroit Lions. Like to me, he I don't
care what team he was on or how long he
played or where he started. He deserves
to be
uh in the Hall of Fame, man. Hell of a
dude, hell of a player, productive that
long, that many years, durability,
production, the whole thing. So,
congrats to him, man. Onward. You played
with him in New York. What kind of
teammate was he? A great teammate, man.
One of those you never forget. Um
Look at him back there. There you go,
brother.
I didn't even see you. Good.
Love you, dude.
He's a great teammate.
He was the guy that he just wanted to
help you. Like you know, whatever help
Like I I'll never forget. I brought this
up. All right, we're playing Washington.
Uh Bruce Smith. We got like a play pass.
He's right on my head. I'm like, okay,
here we go.
Came out. He just swats me, all right?
Bruce Smith just freaking swats me. And
there's LB, dude.
He's there to help me. He's like, I got
you.
You know, um really just covered for me
when really he had another job to do.
He's supposed to kind of help the guard.
He comes back, he helps me, but um
unbelievable teammate, man. Always
upbeat. Uh never bad day. Willing to do
whatever for a teammate. Uh and just a
hell of a player. Hell of a player, man.
Productive player. So, a guy that you
talk about reliability, dependability,
that that was him.
Curious if you got any
um clarification on the the headset
issue from the game. Um I don't even
know who you check in Nope.
Yeah, I man, I haven't had time for any
of that. All right? That's a
I don't know what happened. Um
We asked about it. We don't know. I
don't know what happened.
And you seem to love big stakes, big
ramifications. You seem a little extra
fired up today. Just put into words what
this game means to you and this team
right now. Uh I mean, just it
it's opportunity, you know? Um
And this one's about to be honest again,
which that's exciting. You know, you
ramp it back up. You only got a few
days. You're trying to get everything in
that you can to help your guys get ready
to go. Um
They're in the right mindset. And and
then you just you cut them loose, man.
You let them go. Um let them go play
their game and show up and just compete,
you know? And that's what our guys
that's what they do, man. They do well.
They show up, they compete, man. And uh
So, I I think just big-time opponent,
really good team, division game,
Thanksgiving, first game on,
uh
you couldn't ask for anything better.
When you see more film, how is Micah
Parsons added to that defense? He's a
really good player. He's a great player.
Yeah.
He's a great player.
I like our tackles, all right? I like
our O line. He's a great player.
You had Marcus uh a full participant
practice last week. Uh I'm just curious,
is there a chance you could you could
get him back? And if so, just what kind
of addition would that be?
>> Who's that? Davenport. Yeah, it would be
big to be able to get him back, you
know? Um he he's done a lot to get back.
Uh the amount of work that he's put in
and the amount of rehab um
And look, it's not his fault things have
happened. All you can do is go back to
work and do everything you can to return
uh and get your body uh healed up and
come back better than you were. And he's
done everything that that requires. So,
uh we're hopeful. He walked through
yesterday. He's going to walk through
again today. And we'll see. Just follow
up on
that Khalif left the game the other day.
Where's he at with his ankle injury? Do
you expect him to play on Thursday?
>> a little stiff here. It's a little
stiff, you know? This is uh
you know,
it's a little stiff, little swollen.
There again, it's his uh just see where
he's at really tomorrow. The with the
way the season's gone for you, just all
the challenges, I'm sure it's not
exactly how you would have drawn it up.
Um winning a game the way you won
Sunday,
um does that kind of give you a little
bit more confidence as far as this kind
of like
um survive and advance mentality or just
doing what you need to do to win that
game and move on? Man, I think anytime
you you're able to win a game like that,
uh
you know, things are not going
uh the way that you you want them to
uh and you have to fight your way back
and and just
you know, it it it means that the guys
just stay locked in one more time for
the very next play and believe the next
play is going to is going to break it
open and give you a chance. And I just
think when you're able to come back and
win a game in that fashion,
it it speaks volumes of your team and
where you're at. And uh
I think it's good for you to get those.
You know, you need you need one or two
of those a year. Um
Cuz
you're always tested. Every team gets
tested. And that that one's those are
tough, you know? You're down two scores
in the fourth to be able to
to do what we had to do in all three
phases. I I do think it can pay
dividends for you. We're asking you a
lot.
We're asking you a lot about why won't
you give this guy more touches? Can you
give this guy the ball more? After the
game, Jared said Jamaal Williams is
making a case not just to be one of the
best backs in the league, but one of the
best players in all of football. The
amount of production you're getting out
of him, is he not just this is not just
riding the hot hand, but looking at him
maybe as one of the best players in the
league and and making him if not the
focal point of the offense, certainly
right up there.
Well, you you can't argue with
everything that he's able to do, you
know? He he's a such a versatile player.
Yeah.
You know, and I go I go back to this.
One of the reasons why uh well, there's
many, but that we loved him so much when
he was coming out is that man, he he's
forget the um
which is a huge part of it, the ability
that he has. He's got some rare ability,
but
he
he's smart. He's a football guy. He can
he can retain a lot of information. I
mean, we we put a lot on him now between
the H and the F and playing the receiver
and then he comes back to back.
He he can take all that on and knows all
of it. Knows all those jobs and it
doesn't slow him down. He's got
instincts. He's an instinctive football
player. He's got unbelievable vision for
a runner. He knows how to set up blocks.
And then he's got the explosiveness and
speed to
to finish. So, he's he's got it all, you
know? And he can protect. And he can
So,
um
he's an outstanding player. And
you know, how can you not use the guy
and and get him some touches, you know?
Get him a lot of touches.
Um But you also we got plenty around
him, too. And that's and we're going to
use those guys as well.
And like Brad kind of set it up there
about asking about guys getting touches,
but Isaac has played more right now.
He's got 20 or more snaps each last
three games, but still just four
catches, Dan. Um
I'm curious just your your kind of
assessment of where he's at. We knew it
was kind of a big learning curve for him
with the limited role he had in college.
Um obviously a much bigger playbook in
the NFL. Like where is he at? Where's
your comfort level in in trusting him?
Cuz it seems like he maybe he could help
with some of the vertical elements, some
of the PI stuff that we talked about
last week.
>> Mhm. Just getting him more involved. Uh
we like where Teske is at. He's had a
ton of growth. And look, we went into
this year saying, "Hey, let's let this
guy grow. There would be a place for him
on special teams and he'll be a spot
player on offense." And then once he
proves
that there's more than that, then he
that's what he is until then. Knowing
that man, he's got room to grow and we
love we love the clay. We love to be
able to mold that clay.
And Scotty's done a hell of a job. He's
gotten better and better and better. And
and we are we're we're asking to do
more.
Um and so I I do believe it's it's going
to come. I do believe
he'll get an uptick in production, you
know? He'll get used a little bit more
here. Um
But but I like where he's at. He he's
doing a good job.
Coach,
what's the what's the balance between
trying
to take, you know, take a deep shot just
to kind of
keep the defense a little bit honest,
you know?
And and
and guard against that versus again the
risk involved in
possibly just, you know, trying to
trying to throw it down field.
Yeah, I mean, it's uh
you know, you're always playing that
balance, right? If if you don't take
shots, then they just sit on you. Um and
they can make it difficult, but but also
sometimes you take those shots, you got
to hold the ball for a while, you know?
Depending on what what you really want
to do. So, there is a a risk-reward. And
if you don't, then you got to be able to
within the next two downs, you got to
you got to find a way to convert for the
next round, you know? The next first
down and the next uh
re- reload on the you know, on the
downs. So, um but you got to have both.
You got to be willing to do a little bit
of both.
Defensive, any chance that you guys
would have Kirby on Thursday? Or or
would he need some real practice reps
before going back in a game?
>> Yeah, I don't see Kirby this week.
How how challenging has it been to hold
a guy back who's always raring to go for
you? It's it is it's a it's very
difficult, but but to Kirby's credit,
man, he's he's he is rehabbing. He's
putting in the work. He knows that that
um
the work he's putting in now will
hopefully
keep us from having to play, you know,
this
you know, ride this wave up and down
where okay, he's back, now he's not able
to go. That's that's kind of what all
this is about is man, getting him to a
point we strengthen
uh we strengthen some of these
um you know, stabilize some of this, the
muscles in this area and uh
and get him to where all right, here we
go, man. It doesn't mean it's going to
alleviate some of the pain, but it's
going to make him feel a lot better. And
uh he will be more than functional.
He'll be able to produce and and be
ready for the next week.
Um defensively speaking, third and long
has been an issue all year. Giving up
explosive plays have been a problem all
year. What what what do you need to be
doing better in those situations?
Well, I would say this it's all
I hate to say it, but I am saying it.
It's and it's one thing here, it's one
thing there. And
um some of it has been penalties, you
know, it's the way we play and uh we're
not going to go away from the way we
play.
Um
that's the style that we we're going to
challenge, you know. Uh some of it if we
are going to pressure, we don't always
get home, so I mentioned this the other
day, you get strung out. That happened a
few times. Um
you know, um
we had a couple of things just uh
tackling in space, you know, that got us
and but when you go across the board and
you look at them in totality, it's it's
really one guy here, one guy there.
Um
and so there again, we we just got to
man, we got to play as one. We want them
in second long, we want them in third
and long, so
um we got to be better and we will be
better. We'll be better.
Hate to put you on the spot, but asked a
couple players this yesterday,
Thanksgiving game coming up, what's your
key to the perfect plate?
Key to the perfect plate? Plate. Plate.
Plate. Key to the perfect plate.
Key to the perfect plate.
That's a that's a tough one.
Um
I well, I don't know. I I guess I would
say variety.
It's pretty vanilla, right? It's pretty
boring.
Variety is the key to the
Well, if you're giving me one, give me
ham. Ham is the key, all right, to the
perfect plate. I know there's a lot of
turkey lovers out there.
Um
unless it's fried turkey, I'm all about
fried turkey, but
all right.
[Music]